const quizs = [
    {
      id: 1,
      title: "Kiểm tra an toàn bảo mật thông tin",
      time: 400,
      Point: 250,
      ratings: 4,
      questions: [
        {
          id: 1,
          index: 1,
          question: "Câu 1: Which language runs in a web browser?",
          a: "A. Java",
          b: "B. C",
          c: "C. Python",
          d: "D. JavaScript",
          correct: "d", 
        },
        {
            id: 2,
            index: 2,
            question: "Câu 2: What does CSS stand for?",
            a: "A. Central Style Sheets",
            b: "B. Cascading Style Sheets",
            c: "C. Cascading Simple Sheets",
            d: "D. Cars SUVs Sailboats",
            correct: "b",
          },
          {
            id: 3,
            index: 3,
            question: "Câu 3: What does HTML stand for?",
            a: "A. Hypertext Markup Language",
            b: "B. Hypertext Markdown Language",
            c: "C. Hyperloop Machine Language",
            d: "D. Helicopters Terminals Motorboats Lamborginis",
            correct: "a",
          },
          {
            id: 4,
            index: 4,
            question: "Cấu 4. What year was JavaScript launched?",
            a: "A. 1996",
            b: "B. 1995",
            c: "C. 1994",
            d: "B. none of the above",
            correct: "b",
          },
      ],
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        title: "Kiểm tra 15 phut",
        time: 400,
        Point: 250,
        ratings: 4,
        questions: [
          {
            id: 1,
            index: 1,
            question: "Câu 1: Which language runs in a web browser? 15",
            a: "A. Java",
            b: "B. C",
            c: "C. Python",
            d: "D. JavaScript",
            correct: "d", 
          },
          {
              id: 2,
              index: 2,
              question: "Câu 2: What does CSS stand for 15?",
              a: "A. Central Style Sheets",
              b: "B. Cascading Style Sheets",
              c: "C. Cascading Simple Sheets",
              d: "D. Cars SUVs Sailboats",
              correct: "b",
            },
            {
              id: 3,
              index: 3,
              question: "Câu 3: What does HTML stand for 15?",
              a: "A. Hypertext Markup Language",
              b: "B. Hypertext Markdown Language",
              c: "C. Hyperloop Machine Language",
              d: "D. Helicopters Terminals Motorboats Lamborginis",
              correct: "a",
            },
            {
              id: 4,
              index: 4,
              question: "Cấu 4. What year was JavaScript launched 15?",
              a: "A. 1996",
              b: "B. 1995",
              c: "C. 1994",
              d: "B. none of the above",
              correct: "b",
            },
        ],
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        title: "Kiểm tra 30 phut",
        time: 400,
        Point: 250,
        ratings: 4,
        questions: [
          {
            id: 1,
            index: 1,
            question: "Câu 1: Which language runs in a web browser 30?",
            a: "A. Java",
            b: "B. C",
            c: "C. Python",
            d: "D. JavaScript",
            correct: "d", 
          },
          {
              id: 2,
              index: 2,
              question: "Câu 2: What does CSS stand for 30?",
              a: "A. Central Style Sheets",
              b: "B. Cascading Style Sheets",
              c: "C. Cascading Simple Sheets",
              d: "D. Cars SUVs Sailboats",
              correct: "b",
            },
            {
              id: 3,
              index: 3,
              question: "Câu 3: What does HTML stand for 30?",
              a: "A. Hypertext Markup Language",
              b: "B. Hypertext Markdown Language",
              c: "C. Hyperloop Machine Language",
              d: "D. Helicopters Terminals Motorboats Lamborginis",
              correct: "a",
            },
            {
              id: 4,
              index: 4,
              question: "Cấu 4. What year was JavaScript launched 30?",
              a: "A. 1996",
              b: "B. 1995",
              c: "C. 1994",
              d: "B. none of the above",
              correct: "b",
            },
        ],
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        title: "Kiểm tra 40",
        time: 400,
        Point: 250,
        ratings: 4,
        questions: [
          {
            id: 1,
            index: 1,
            question: "Câu 1: Which language runs in a web browser 40?",
            a: "A. Java",
            b: "B. C",
            c: "C. Python",
            d: "D. JavaScript",
            correct: "d", 
          },
          {
              id: 2,
              index: 2,
              question: "Câu 2: What does CSS stand for 40?",
              a: "A. Central Style Sheets",
              b: "B. Cascading Style Sheets",
              c: "C. Cascading Simple Sheets",
              d: "D. Cars SUVs Sailboats",
              correct: "b",
            },
            {
              id: 3,
              index: 3,
              question: "Câu 3: What does HTML stand for 40?",
              a: "A. Hypertext Markup Language",
              b: "B. Hypertext Markdown Language",
              c: "C. Hyperloop Machine Language",
              d: "D. Helicopters Terminals Motorboats Lamborginis",
              correct: "a",
            },
            {
              id: 4,
              index: 4,
              question: "Cấu 4. What year was JavaScript launched 40?",
              a: "A. 1996",
              b: "B. 1995",
              c: "C. 1994",
              d: "B. none of the above",
              correct: "b",
            },
        ],
      },
  ];
  
  export default quizs;
  